야야 내가 드라마야
Ya Ya I’m the Drama
Ziggy ziggy zag 난 처음이야
Ziggy ziggy zag I’m new
왜냐면 난 비기비기나쁘게 가거든 그건 사실이야
Cause I go biggie biggie bad It’s true
날카로운 눈빛에 유독
Sharp eye, inside it's Toxic
본능을 깨워라 Zoom
Zoom in, pull on my instincts
잠깐만, 뭐야?
Hold up, What? Oh my god
당신은 상처받을 것이라고 말합니다.
You say, What? You gon' get hurt
조심하는 게 좋을 거야
You better watch out
우리는 멈출 수 없는 Boom
We already that big, tough Boom
과속하는 브룸
Racing with that big, bad Vroom
난 내가 굴러다니는 걸 좋아해
I li-li like me when I roll
Li-li- 내가 야만적일 때 나를 좋아해
Li-li-like me when I’m savage
Li-li-내가 갈 때 나를 좋아해
Li-li-like me when I go
내가 가장 나빴을 때 Li-li-likee
Li-li-likie when I baddest
잠깐만 빛을 따라가
Hold up, chasing lights
달리고, 달리고, 달리고
Racing lights, run, run on, Run
드디어 가 라타타타
Go Finally Ra ta ta ta
다음 세상을 열어본다
Open up a new world, boom-ta-da
1, 2 이제 갈 시간이야
1, 2 It’s time to go
나는 후회하지 않는다
Regrets, ain't got 'em
용감하게 맞서다가 완전히 무너졌어
Square up, I break 'em
나를 따르는 규칙
Rules, they gon' follow me
손끝으로 탭하여 세상을 바꾸세요
Tap my finger and watch the world move
응, 갈 거야
Yeah I’m coming
가져오다 가져오다
I bring I bring
모든 드라마-마-마-마
all the Drama-ma-ma-ma
드라마마마마 가져왔어요
I bring Drama-ma-ma-ma
내 여자들을 뒤에 두고
With my girls in the back
뒤에 여자
Girls in the back
드라마
Drama
트라우마 마마 마
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
나는 Trauma-ma-ma-ma를 깨뜨린다
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma
MY WORLD를 뒤쪽에 두고
With MY WORLD in the back
내 드라마부터 시작해
It starts with me, Drama
(그 모든 것)
(All that)
드라마-마-마-마
Drama-ma-ma-ma
(그걸 가져와)
(Bring it that)
드라마-마-마-마
Drama-ma-ma-ma
내 여자들을 뒤에 두고
With my girls in the back
뒤에 있는 여자들 Yeah
Girls in the back Yeah
나는 부서진다
I break
트라우마 마마 마
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
(우리는)
(We them)
트라우마 마마 마
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
MY WORLD를 뒤쪽에 두고
With MY WORLD in the back
내 드라마부터 시작해
It starts with me, Drama
드라마-마-마-마
Drama-ma-ma-ma
드라마마마마(3, 2, 1)
Drama-ma-ma-ma (3, 2, 1)
드라마마마
Drama-ma-ma
내가 이런 식이었다는 걸 알잖아
You know I’ve been kind of like
1, 2, 3 다음 장면은 놀라움으로 가득하다
1, 2, 3, cue that jump-scare Scene
열쇠를 들고
Who's got the key?
주인공은 나야
Main character, that's me
4, 3, 2 내려가는 중
4, 3, 2 Going down
쉽게 통해
Breezin' Through
데자뷰처럼
Just like Deja Vu
완성된 그림
They picture my image
일부러 막지 마세요
Don't try to stop me
이게 내 드라마야
This is my Drama
고의로 멈추거나 자극하지 않을 것입니다.
Pull up if you wanna
Uh 난 정말 대단해
Uh I’m a stunner
1, 2 이제 갈 시간이야
1, 2 It’s time to go
불안한 나를 (불타오르게 하는 나를)
I ignite (I shine bright)
나는 그것을 느낄 수 있고 나는 그것을 좋아합니다
Feelin' it, And I love it
규칙의 새로운 모습
New game, new Rules
눈을 떠요 (눈을 떠요)
I open my eyes (open my eyes)
(너는) 시작된 걸 알잖아 (이제)
Game on, (you) know it (Now)
오고있다
It’s coming
가져오다 가져오다
I bring I bring
모든 드라마-마-마-마
all the Drama-ma-ma-ma
드라마마마마 가져왔어요
I bring Drama-ma-ma-ma
내 여자들을 뒤에 두고
With my girls in the back
뒤에 여자
Girls in the back
드라마
Drama
트라우마 마마 마
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
나는 Trauma-ma-ma-ma를 깨뜨린다.
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma
MY WORLD를 뒤쪽에 두고
With MY WORLD in the back
내 드라마부터 시작해
It starts with me, Drama
실제 세계로
Into the REAL WORLD
클라이맥스의 도착
Climax on deck
두려워하지 마세요
Don't be afraid
너와 나
You and I
함께 계속되는 이야기
Together we write this Story
한때 나를 가로막았던 No를 넘어
Past hurdles, No more
극한의 매일
Push boundaries Every day
오 내 방식대로 할 거야
Oh Imma make it my way
방해가 되지 않아 그래
Out of the way Yeah
가져오다 가져오다
I bring I bring
모든 드라마-마-마-마
all the Drama-ma-ma-ma
드라마마마마 가져왔어요
I bring Drama-ma-ma-ma
내 여자들을 뒤에 두고
With my girls in the back
뒤에있는 소녀들
Girls in the back
드라마
Drama
트라우마 마마 마
Trauma-ma-ma-ma
나는 Trauma-ma-ma-ma를 깨뜨린다.
I break Trauma-ma-ma-ma
MY WORLD를 뒤쪽에 두고
With MY WORLD in the back
나랑 드라마
It stays with me, Drama
(그 모든 것)
(All that)
알잖아, 난 야만적이야
You know, I’m savage
양심의 가책 없이 Baddest
Unstoppable, Baddest
나를 둘러싼 스릴
All wrapped in Thrill
힘든 여정을 그린 드라마
Bumpy off-road Drama
(드라마마마)
(Drama-ma-ma)
내가 깨뜨리는 모든 것 트라우마
I'll break this cycle of Trauma
(드라마마마)
(Drama-ma-ma)
지금부터 시작하는 드라마
It starts now, Drama
Ya Ya는 MY Drama로 시작됩니다
Ya Ya, It starts with you, MY Drama